Guide to the New York University Archives Audiovisual Collection AV
New York University Archives
- Audiovisual Recordings
  - Highlights in Jazz #14: Odetta, David Amram, Pepper Adams, Jerry Dodgion, Herb Bushler, Al Harewood, 1974-05-06; cuid656; Kleinsinger, Jack; Amram, David; Odetta, 1930-2008; 2 Half_Inch_Video_Reel (Box 53, Reel 2908, Box 156, Reel 2909)
    Transfer Technician Notes AV2909: "This tape suffers from severe inherent sync errors that result in persistent image jitter and a high head switch error. Multiple captures were performed using combinations of different capture decks and TBCs, and this file represents the best capture possible. Aside from the aforementioned errors, glare from Odetta's guitar triggers an auto-exposure response from the TBC that severely dims the picture. Again, this error was troubleshooted using multiple TBCs, and could not be corrected. The glare occasionally clips the luma. Occasional tape wear and damage occur throughout. Audio distortion is inherent to original recording."
  - Highlights in Jazz #14: Odetta, David Amram, Pepper Adams, Jerry Dodgion, Herb Bushler, Al Harewood (Tape 3 of 3), 6 May 1974; AV2910; 1 Half_Inch_Video_Reel (Box 156, Reel 2910)
    Tape labeled Tape 3 of 3. This is the only recording that the University Archives has of this event.
    Original format: 1/2 inch open reel video; Transfer Technician Notes: "Content plays generally well throughout, however the glare from Odetta's guitar triggers an autoexposure response from the TBC that repeatedly dims the image. Her performance here (as well as on another tape) were captured using multiple TBCs, and this file represents the most satisfactory transfer, despite the luma error. Elsewhere, there are occasional dropouts and tape wear, along with recurring image jitter. Persistent edge wear throughout, as well as visible head switching."
  - Highlights in Jazz: Latin Jam, 7 October 1974; cuid657; Kleinsinger, Jack; 2 Half_Inch_Video_Reel (Box 156, Reel 2911, 2912)
    Original format: 1/2 inch open reel video; Transfer Technician Notes AV2911: "As with other tapes in this collection, there is an inherent constant sync error that is stabilized by time base correction, but ultimately results in moderate to severe flagging and mild image jitter throughout. Elsewhere, there are occasional mild dropouts and tape wear. There exists one extended instance of tape creasing. Occasional inherent exposure adjustments and mild ghosting. Luma is adjusted to mitigate clipping from glare. There are occasional instances of high frequency noise and mild audio distortion inherent to the content."
    Transfer Technician Notes AV2912: "Entirety of tape suffers from a constant control track error. Multiple TBCs were tested to obtain the best capture possible. Content suffers from persistent flagging throughout, as a result of the inherent control track error. Recurring mild tape wear and dropouts throughout, and occasional mild tape damage. Mild audio distortion is inherent to original recording."
  - NYU football, undated; AV2913; 1 film reels (Box 79, Reel 2913)
    Related Materials
    This item is related to RG41: Records of the Department of Athletics.
    Football.; New York University -- Sports
  - Berlin Olympics 1936, AV2914; 16 mm film (Film canister UA2914)
    This material is related to RG 41, Records of the Department of Athletics
    Olympics.
  - NYU vs. unknown opponent (football) (11), AV2915; 1 film reels; Original Film is B&W, Silent; 16 mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2915 / Av_ref820)
    This item is related to RG 41, records of the Department of Athletics
  - NYU vs. unknown opponent (football) (17), AV2916; 1 film reels; 16 mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2916)
  - NYU vs Holy Cross, unknown; AV2917; 1 film reels (Box 78, Reel AV2917)
    New York University -- Sports
  - NYU vs. St. Louis University, 15 January 1952; AV2918; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16 mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2918 / Av_ref832)
    Basketball.; Madison Square Garden. (New York, N.Y.: 1925-1968); New York University -- Sports
  - NYU vs. Dartmouth College, 2 January 1950; AV2919; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16 mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2919 / Av_ref835)
  - NYU vs. Carnegie Mellon University, 1936; AV2920; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2920 / Av_ref933)
    This item is related to RG41, records of the Department of Athletics
  - NYU vs. University of Illinois, 26 December 1964; AV2921; 1 film reels; 8 mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2921 / Av_ref841)
    This item is related to RG 41, the records of the Department of Athletics
    Basketball.; NYU Press
  - NYU vs. Dartmouth College, 2 January 1949; AV2922; 1 film reels; 16 mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2922 / Av_ref844)
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame, 27 February 1950; AV2923; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16 mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2923 / Av_ref847)
    This item is related to RG 41: Records of the Department of Athletics.
  - NYU vs. University of North Carolina, 1949; AV2924; 1 film reels; 16 mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2924 / Av_ref850)
    Basketball.; New York University -- Sports
  - NYU vs. St. Louis University, 15 January 1952; AV2925; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16 mm film (Box 164, Reel AV2925 / Av_ref853)
  - NYU vs. LaSalle College, 1961; AV2926; 1 film reels; 8 mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2926 / Av_ref856)
    This reel depicts a scrimmage.
  - NYU vs. Colgate University, 1950; AV2927; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16 mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2927 / Av_ref859)
    This item is related to RG 41, records of the Department of Athletics.
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame, 1951 February 26; AV2928; 1 film reels; 16mm film
  - NYU vs. St. Louis University, 15 January 1952; AV2929; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16 mm film; Reel is labeled Reel #2. (Box 78, Reel AV2929 / Av_ref865)
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame, 1951 February 26; AV2930; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2930 / Av_ref949)
  - NYU vs. University of North Carolina, 1946; AV2931; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 78, Reel AV2931 / Av_ref939)
  - NYU vs. Yale University (JV), 23 October 1964; AV2932; 1 film reels; 16 mm film (Box 158, Reel AV2932 / Av_ref874)
  - NYU vs. Yale University (JV), 23 October 1964; AV2933; 1 film reels; 16 mm film (Box 158, Reel AV2933 / Av_ref877)
    This film comprises the second part of the game on Reel 2932.
  - NYU vs. Brigham Young University, 19 March 1966; AV2934; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 164, Reel AV2934 / Av_ref880)
  - NYU vs. Southern Methodist University, 1946-1947; AV2935; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 158, Reel AV2935 / Av_ref883)
  - NYU vs. University of North Carolina (Reel 1), 1949; AV2936; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 158, Reel AV2936 / Av_ref986)
    This item is related to RG 41.4, Records of the Football Program, Department of Athletics.
  - NYU vs. University of Texas (Reel 3), 1948; AV2937; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 158, Reel AV2937 / Av_ref989)
  - NYU vs. University of North Carolina (Reel 3), 1949; AV2938; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 158, Reel AV2938 / Av_ref992)
  - NYU vs. Yale University (Reel 1), 1948; AV2939; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Reel AV2939)
  - The City and the University, undated; AV2940; 1 film reels (Box 78, Reel 2940)
    Original format: 16 mm composite b/w print
    This item has not yet been digitized.
  - NYU vs. Fordham University (Reel 3), 1948; AV2941; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,941)
  - Jamestown (2 of 4), unknown; AV2942; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 158, Reel AV2942 / Av_ref968)
  - Jamestown (1 of 4), unknown; AV2943; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 158, Reel 2,943)
  - NYU vs. Fordham University (Reel 2), 1948; AV2944; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 158, Reel 2,944)
  - NYU vs. Fordham University (Reel 1), 1948; AV2945; 1 film reels
    - Original Recording (Box 79, 16mm film reels 2945)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Dvd 12:17)
  - Hobart College vs. Virginia Wesleyan, 1930; AV2946; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,946)
  - NYU vs. Georgetown University, 1948; AV2947; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Reel AV2947)
  - NYU Commencements, 1953-1966; AV2948; 1 film reels; 8mm
    - Original Recording (Box 158, 8mm film reel 2948)
    - Access Copy (Box 123, Disc 2948)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Dvd 11:19)
  - NYU v. Hobart College (football), 1932; AV2949; 1 film reels (Box 158, Reel 2949)
    This material is related to RG 41.4, Records of the Football Program, Department of Athletics.
    Technical requirements
    Original format: 16mm film
  - MN-1319b: Basic Swimming Techniques--Elementary Tactics of Life Saving, undated; AV2950; 1 film reels; 16mm film; Container label reads: "United States Navy, Bureau of Aeronautics. Training Film Section, Photographic Division." (Box 81, Reel 2,950)
  - NYU vs. Dartmouth College, 2 January 1950; AV2951; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 158, Reel 2,951)
  - NYU basketball, unknown; AV2952; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 158, Reel AV2952 / Av_ref912)
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame, 1950 February 27; AV2953; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 158, Reel AV2953 / Av_ref1001)
  - NYU basketball, undated; AV2954; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Reel AV2954)
    Condition Note
    This film has severe Vinegar Syndrome. It is too warped to inspect or remove from the reel. CANNOT BE LOOKED AT.
  - Sunrise Semester: Middle East (Reel 1 of 2), 1950; AV2955; 1 film reels; 16mm film
  - Sunrise Semester: Middle East (Reel 2 of 2), 1950; AV2956; 1 film reels; 16 mm film
  - NYU vs. Southern Methodist University (Reel 3), 1946-1947; AV2957; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2957 / Av_ref1012)
  - NYU vs. Fordham University, 1951; AV2958; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 2,958)
  - Berlin Olympics (track, gymnastics), 1936; AV2959; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Film canister UA2959)
    Olympics.; Gymnastics.; New York University -- Sports
  - NYU vs. University of Oklahoma, 1951 December 22; AV2960; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2960 / Av_ref921)
  - NYU vs. Southern Methodist University (Reel 2), 1946-1947; AV2961; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2961 / Av_ref1018)
  - NYU vs. Colgate University, 1950 December 12; AV2962; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2962 / Av_ref1021)
  - University of Cincinnati vs. St. Bonaventure University, 1957-1958; AV2963; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2963 / Av_ref1024)
  - NYU football practice, undated; AV2964; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,964)
  - NYU vs. City College of New York, undated; AV2965; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2965 / Av_ref924)
  - NYU vs. Villanova University, 1930; AV2966; 1 film reels (Box 160, Reel AV2966 / Av_ref677)
  - NYU vs. Syracuse University, 1940-1941; AV2967; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,967)
    This item is related to RG41, records of the Department of Athletics.
  - NYU vs. PMC, 1940; AV2968; 1 film reels; 16mm film; Container label reads: #28 (Box 81, Reel 2,968)
  - NYU vs. Georgetown Football, 1940; AV2969; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 79, Reel AV2969)
  - NI-1, unknown; AV2970; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2970 / Av_ref909)
  - NYU vs. Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey, 1930; AV2971; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2971)
  - NYU vs. Brigham Young University (Reel 1), 19 March 1966; AV2972; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2972 / Av_ref1033)
    This item is related to RG 41.1, Records of the Basketball Program, Department of Athletics.
  - NYU v. Pennsylvania State University (football), 1929; AV2973; 1 film reels (Box 160, Reel AV2973 / Av_ref674)
  - NYU v. Georgetown University (football), 1932; AV2974; 1 film reels (Box 79, Reel 2974)
    Original format 16mm film.
  - [Unidentified Loop], unknown; AV2975; 1 film loops; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2975 / Av_ref903)
  - NYU vs. University of Oregon (Reel 3), 1946-47; AV2976; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2976 / Av_ref1036)
  - NYU vs. University of Oregon (Reel 2), 1946; AV2977; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2977 / Av_ref1039)
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame (Reel 3), 1947; AV2978; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 160, Reel AV2978 / Av_ref1042)
  - NYU vs. Syracuse University, 17 December 1959; AV2979; 1 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2979)
    Madison Square Garden. (New York, N.Y.: 1925-1968); New York University -- Sports
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame, 1949-50; AV2980; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 159, Reel AV2980 / Av_ref1048)
    This item is related to RG41, records of the Deparment of Athletics
  - NYU vs. Duke University, 1946-47; AV2981; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 159, Reel AV2981 / Av_ref1051)
  - NYU vs. Colgate University, 12 December 1950; AV2982; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 159, Reel AV2982 / Av_ref1054)
  - NYU vs. Duke University (Reel 1), 1946-47; AV2983; 1 film reels; 16mm film; Container label reads: 30-31 (Box 159, Reel AV2983 / Av_ref1057)
    This item is related to RG 41, Records of the Department of Athletics.
  - NYU vs. Duke University (Reel 2), undated; AV2984; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 159, Reel AV1984 / AV_ref1060)
    This item relates to RG 41, Records of the Department of Athletics.
  - unknown sports film, undated; AV2985; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 164, Reel 2,985)
  - NYU 1-2 (L. Winik), unknown; AV2986; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 159, Reel AV2986 / Av_ref906)
  - NYU football [N1-12], undated; AV2989; 1 film reels; 16mm film
  - [#21 Football], unknown; AV2990; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 159, Reel AV2990 / Av_ref918)
  - NYU vs. West Virginia Wesleyan University, 13 October 1934; AV2991; 1 film reels (Box 79, Reel 2991)
    Original format: 16mm film, positive, b&w, acetate, 300 ft, mild wear, some smudging on base, 0.5% shrinkage, silent
  - NYU vs. Pennsylvania State University, October 19, 1929; AV2992; 1 film reels (Box 79, 16mm film reels 2992, Box Shared University Archives 115, Dvd 12:14-12:15)
    Football.; New York University -- Sports; Yankee Stadium (New York, N.Y.: 1923-2009)
    - Film Positive (Box 79, 16mm film reels 2992)
      Original format: 16mm film, positive, black and white, acetate, 400 ft, bad perforation/tear halfway through (unrepairable), 1.3% shrinkage, condition information per film lab inspection report, 5/10/2012
    - Access Copies (Box Shared University Archives 115, Dvd 12:14-12:15)
  - NYU football, unknown; AV2993; 1 film reels (Box Shared University Archives 137, Reel AV 2993)
  - NYU student demonstrations, October 17, 1968; AV2994; 1 film reels
    - Original Recording (Box Shared University Archives 137, Super 8mm film reel AV 2994)
    - Access Copies (Box Shared University Archives 115, Dvd 12:18-12:19)
  - Washington Square Campus, unknown; AV2995; 1 film reels; 16mm film
  - NYU - Washington Square, 1968 October 14; AV2996; 1 film reels (Box Shared University Archives 140, Quarter inch audio reel AV2996)
  - NYU Bronx, unknown; AV2997; 1 sound tape reels; 1/4" Open Reel Audio (Box Shared University Archives 140, Quarter inch audio reel AV2997)
  - NYU football, undated; AV2998; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 159, Reel AV2998 / Av_ref1074)
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame, 1948; AV2999; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 2,999)
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame, 1948; AV3000; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 164, Reel AV3000 / Av_ref1173)
    Reel labeled Reel #3.
  - NYU vs. University of Oklahoma, 1951 December 22; AV3001; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 159, Reel AV3001 / Av_ref1088)
  - NYU vs. Lafayette College, undated; AV3002; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box Shared University Archives 137, Reel AV 3002)
  - NYU football, undated; AV3003; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 3,003)
    This item relates to RG41, records of the Department of Athletics
  - NYU vs. Temple University, undated; AV3004; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 78, Reel 3,004)
  - NYU wrestling, undated; AV3005; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 3,005)
  - NYU wrestling, undated; AV3006; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 3,006)
  - NYU Heights Campus, 17 November 1968; AV3007; 1 film reels; 16mm film
  - NYU Washington Square Campus, Nov 17 1968; AV3008; 1 film reels; 16mm film
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame, 6 January 1953; AV3009; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Box 79, Reel AV3009 / Av_ref886)
    Reel depicts second half of game.
  - NYU vs. Manhattan College, 12 February 1953; AV3010; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16 mm film (Box 159, Reel AV3010 / Av_ref889)
    Reel depicts first half of game.
  - NYU vs. University of Illinois, Springfield, 1948; AV3011; 1 film reels
  - NYU vs. University of Michigan, December 26, 1963; AV3012; Rush Sports Films; 1 film reels
    This film depicts a game at the L.A. Classic.
    Basketball.; Rossini, Lou; University of Michigan; New York University -- Sports
    - Original Recording (Box 164, 16mm film reels AV3012 / Av_ref893)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Dvd 12:16)
  - University of Pennsylvania vs. Columbia University, 1955-56; AV3013; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Reel AV3013)
    Basketball.; University of Pennsylvania; Columbia University
  - Columbia University vs. Princeton University, 8 January 1957; AV3014; Winik Films Corporation; 1 film reels; 16mm film (Reel AV3014)
    The game was played at Princeton University's Dillon Gymnasium.
    Basketball.; Princeton University; Columbia University; New York University -- Sports
  - Dinner and Presentation of the New York University Gallatin Medal to Richard Courant, 1967; AV3016; Gallatin Associates; 2 Sound_Disc--Vinyl (Box Shared University Archives 106, Disc 8, Disc 9, Box 83A, Item 3016)
    Access copies are available for this recording.
    This recording is related to materials in RG 37.18, Records of the Albert Gallatin Associates, RG 46.8, Records of the Presentation of University Awards, and MC 150, the Richard Courant Papers.
    Mathematics.; Courant, Richard, 1888-1972
  - Interview with President Oliva, 8 August 1995; AV3113 - AV3116; Oliva, L. Jay (Lawrence Jay), 1933-2014; 4 VHS (Box 86, Cassette 3,113-3,116)
    This material is related to RG 6.0.8, Records of the Office of the Chancellor and/or Executive Vice President (Oliva) and RG 3.0.11, Records of the Office of the President (Oliva).
    Tapes 2-4 of this recording have been digitized. Please contact the University Archives for access.
  - The Miracle at Washington Square, undated; AV3145 (Box 87, Item 3145)
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (final lecture) (tape 1 of 9), 19 December 1963A; AV3147; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3147)
    Physical/Technical Notes
    Original format: 1/4" open reel Original stock: Scotch 1.5 mil acetate, 7" reel Barcode: 31142046549534
    The University Archives does not have tapes representing lectures 1, 6, and 7 in this series.
    Titian, approximately 1488-1576
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture 11) (tape 2 of 9), 12 December 1963; AV3148; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3148)
    Original format: 1/4" open reel Original stock: Scotch 1.5 mil acetate, 7" reel
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture 10) (tape 3 of 9), 15 December [1963]; AV3149; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3149)
    Original format: 1/4" open reel Original stock: Scotch 1.5 mil acetate, 7" reel barcode: 31142046549526
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture 9) (tape 4 of 9), 1963 November 14; AV3150; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3150)
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture 8) (tape 5 of 9), [1963]; AV3151; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3151)
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture V) (tape 6 of 9), [1963]; AV3152 (Box 87, Reel 3152)
    Titian, approximately 1488-1576; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture IV) (tape 7 of 9), [1963]; AV3153 (Box 87, Reel 3153)
    Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968; Titian, approximately 1488-1576
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture 3) (tape 8 of 9), [1963]; AV3154; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3154)
  - Lecture: Erwin Panofsky on Titian (Lecture II, Tape 9 of 9), [1963]; AV3155; Panofsky, Erwin, 1892-1968 (Box 87, Reel 3155)
  - MacNeil/Lehrer Newshour: Galway, AV3272; Brademas, John, 1927-2016 (Box 90, Item 3272)
  - Today Show, AV3273; Brademas, John, 1927-2016 (Box 90, Item 3273)
  - First-year report on $100 million fundraising drive, AV3274; Brademas, John, 1927-2016 (Box 90, Item 3274)
  - New Day Chicago (WBBM-TV): "Dr. Brademas, President of NYU", AV3275; Brademas, John, 1927-2016 (Box 90, Item 3275)
  - Face the Nation (CBS-TV), AV3276 (Box 90, Item 3276)
  - In the Year 2000: Craig Claiborne, circa 1967; AV3; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 124, Reel 3)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:38)
  - In the Year 2000: Frank Elli -- Prisons, February 6, 1968; AV5; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 124, Reel 5)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:51)
  - In the Year 2000: Morris Ernst, circa 1967; AV6; 1 sound tape reels (Box 124, Reel 6, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 3)
    Access copy available on CD: 13:3
    Original tape box labeled with note "Speed change"
  - In the Year 2000: Frank W. Notestein -- Population Council, circa 1967; AV15; 1 sound tape reels
    Original tape box labeled with note "Good interview"
    - Original Recording (Box 124, Reel 15)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:46)
  - In the Year 2000: Randolph Theron -- Medicine in the Year 2000, April 29, 1968; AV17; 1 sound tape reels
    Original tape box includes note "Chee[?] 211."
    - Original Recording (Box 124, Reel 17)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:22)
  - In the Year 2000: Victor Riesel, circa 1967; AV18; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 124, Reel 18)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:47)
  - In the Year 2000: Jackie Robinson, circa 1967; AV19; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 124, Reel 19)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:48)
  - In the Year 2000: Paul Shepard, circa 1967; AV24; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 124, Reel 24)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:21)
  - In the Year 2000: Lee Strasberg, Dr. Mary Calderone, circa 1967; AV26; 1 sound tape reels (Box 124, Reel 26, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 1)
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 13:1
  - In the Year 2000: John Yocum, Lamont Cole, May 24, 1968; AV28; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 124, Reel 28)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:28)
  - In the Year 2000: By the Year 2000 edited master reel 1, circa 1967; AV303; 1 sound tape reels (Box Digitized Access Files, Reel AV303)
    Original tape box includes notes "Yr 2000 edited master reel 1," "Harrington Master 4:08"
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Reel 303)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:41)
  - In the Year 2000: By the Year 2000 edited master reel 2, circa 1967; AV304; 1 sound tape reels (Box Digitized Access Files, E-records AV304)
    Original tape box includes following note: "By the Year 2000 edited master reel 2"
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Reel 304)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:37)
  - In the Year 2000: By the Year 2000 edited master reel 3, circa 1967; AV305; 1 sound tape reels (Box Digitized Access Files, E-records AV305)
    Original tape box includes following notes: "Tebbel 3:26," "By the Yr 2000 edited master reel 3"
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Reel 305)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:36)